skeleton: n.   骷髅, seemingly: adv. 表面上地, respectable: adj. 体面的，雅观的
Lesson 24. A skeleton in the cupboard. We often read in novels how a seemingly respectable
第24课。橱柜中的骨骼。我们经常读小说中看似受人尊敬的
conceal: v.   隐藏，隐瞒
person or family has some terrible secret which has been concealed from strangers for years.
人或家人有一个可怕的秘密，多年来一直被陌生人隐藏。
vivid: adj. 生动的
The English language possesses a vivid saying to describe this sort of situation.
英语具有生动的说法来描述这种情况。
skeleton: n.   骷髅, dramatic: adj. 令人激动的，扣人心弦的
The terrible secret is called a skeleton in the cupboard. At some dramatic moment in the story,
可怕的秘密称为橱柜中的骨骼。在故事中的某个戏剧性时刻，
ruin: v.   毁坏
the terrible secret becomes known and a reputation is ruined. The reader's hair stands on end
可怕的秘密已知，声誉被毁了。读者的头发直立
heroine: n.   女主人公
when he reads in the final pages of the novel that the heroine uh. Dear old lady who had always
当他在小说的最后一页上读到女主人公时。亲爱的老太太
been so kind to everybody, had, in her youth, poisoned every one of her five husbands.
对每个人都如此友善，在她的青年时代，她毒害了五个丈夫中的每一个。
fiction: n.   小说, varying: adj. 不同的
It is all very well for such things to occur in fiction. To varying degrees, we all have secrets
这些事情在小说中都很好。在不同程度上，我们都有秘密
skeleton: n.   骷髅
which we do not want even our closest friends to learn. But few of us have skeletons in the cupboard.
我们甚至不希望我们最亲密的朋友学习。但是我们当中很少有人在橱柜里有骨骼。
skeleton: n.   骷髅
The only person I know who has a skeleton in the cupboard is George Carlton. And he is very
我认识的唯一在橱柜里有骨骼的人是乔治·卡尔顿（George Carlton）。他非常
medicine: n.   医学
pound of the fact. George studied medicine in his youth. Instead of becoming a doctor. However,
事实。乔治在年轻时学习医学。而不是成为医生。然而，
he became a successful writer of detective stories. I once spend an uncomfortable weekend which I
他成为侦探故事的成功作家。我曾经度过一个不舒服的周末
shall never forget at his house. George showed me to the guest room which. He said, was rarely used.
永远不会在他的房子里忘记。乔治把我带到了客房。他说，很少使用。
unpack: vt.  （从箱中）取出, stack: v.   （整齐地）堆放，排放
He told me to unpack my things and then come down to dinner. After I had stacked my shirts and
他告诉我要解开我的东西，然后下来吃饭。在我堆叠衬衫之后，
underclothes: n.   内衣, drawer: n.   抽屉
underclothes in two empty drawers. I decided to hang one of the toe suits I had brought with me in
两个空抽屉中的底衣服。我决定挂在我带上的一件脚趾西装中
the cupboard. I opened the cupboard door and then stood in front of two suits I had brought with me
橱柜。我打开橱柜门，然后站在我带上的两套西装前
in the cupboard. I opened the cupboard door and then stood in front of its suits I had brought with
在橱柜里。我打开橱柜门，然后站在我带上的西装前
skeleton: n.   骷髅
me in the cupboard. I opened the cupboard door and then stood in front of it petrified. A skeleton
我在橱柜里。我打开了橱柜门，然后站在它的前面。骨骼
sway: v.   摇摆
was dangling before my eyes. The sudden movement of the door made its sway slightly and it gave me
在我眼前晃来晃去。门的突然动作使它略微摇摆，这给了我
the impression that it was. About to leap out at me. Dropping my suit, I dashed downstairs to tell
那是印象。即将向我跳出来。放下衣服，我在楼下说话
skeleton: n.   骷髅, unsympathetic: adj. 不表同情的，无动于衷的
George. This was worse than a terrible secret. This was a read skeleton. But George was unsympathetic.
乔治。这比一个可怕的秘密还要糟糕。这是一个读的骨骼。但是乔治并不同情。
Oh, that, he said with a smile as if he were talking about an old friend. That's Sebastian. You
哦，那他笑着说，好像他在谈论一个老朋友。那是塞巴斯蒂安。你
medical: adj. 医学的
forget that I was a medical student once upon a time.
忘了我曾经是一名医学生。